Okorafor Chidinma Christiana

Lagos, Nigeria | okoraforchidinma12@gmail.com | 08165381950

Profile

I am a results-driven professional with a background in product management and technical support. I have extensive experience in ensuring product quality, resolving technical challenges, and delivering exceptional customer experiences. I have built passion projects that helped me understand the engineering side of things while communicating with the engineering team.

Education

B.Eng. Electronic Engineering - University of Nigeria, Nsukka	2014-2020
MENG Systems Management- University of Lagos.	Inview

Certification

Product Launches, Roadmapping, Strategy, Analytics, Product School- Interswitch Job

Shadowing	2024
SKF Distributor College—SKF	2020-2023
Google Cloud – Coursera	2020
Fundamentals of Project Management—Coursera	2020
Fundamentals of Microsoft Office – New Horizon	2017

Technical Skills

- Microsoft Office 365, Exchange Online, OneDrive for Business, Teams, PowerShell, Active Directory, DNS
- Agile and Scrum Methodologies
- Jira, ClickUp, Productboard, Mixpanel
- css, javascript, git, React(material ui, radix ui, Next.js)

Soft Skills

- Process Documentation
- Team Collaboration
- Self-driven to provide a timely solution
- Exceptional Verbal and Written Communication Skills

My Passion Project Link.

https://dymacode.github.io/learning-portfolio/

Work History

Product Manager- Regxta

12/2023-Present

- Directly managing 11 developers while addressing daily challenges to ensure product quality as well as accelerated issue resolution by 25%
- Crafted Product Requirement Document to scope and manage the launch of the Regxta version 2.0 within the 1st Quarter.
- I handle data and user feedback to improve product features, resulting in a 4% increase in Netprofit.
- I create user stories and tickets on Jira and assign these tasks to the required development team.

Technical Support Engineer- Tek Experts Nigeria

07/2023-12/2023

- I provided technical support to clients via phone and email, resolving issues promptly and ensuring customer satisfaction.
- Diagnosed software problems and troubleshoot technical issues related to Microsoft 365 applications that use these products in the NOAM region(USA, Canada).
- I collaborated with the development team to escalate and resolve complex technical issues, contributing to product improvement.
- I documented support processes and created knowledge base articles for common issues, reducing resolution time.

Customer Service – FirstAdvancetek Solutions Limited, Lagos

09/2020-06/2023

- I provided Technical Support for SKF bearings, lubricants, maintenance tools, etc., to customers to keep customers satisfied.
- Processed documentation for tracking the progress of SKF products and completed 93% on-time delivery.
- I conducted initial Product analysis for companies to determine their needs.
- Implemented product changes and recommendations for customers.

Information Technology Intern – Alpha Mead Group, Lagos

06/2017 - 11/2017

- I installed and configured computer hardware, software, systems, networks, printers, and scanners, and set up accounts for new users.
- Troubleshoot and resolve complex technical issues related to M365 services, including user management, email routing, calendar sharing, site collection configuration, and data loss prevention.
- I collaborated with team members to deliver technical solutions and training materials to staff on using the Softphone.